/*    $.each(questions[id].answers, function (key, value) {

        var answerButton = $(document.createElement('a'));
        answerButton.addClass('btn btn-primary btn-lg btn-answer');
        answerButton.text(value);
        answerButton.attr('data-correct', questions[id].rightAnswer);
        answerButton.attr('data-answer', key);
        answerButton.attr('data-question', id);
//            answerButton.attr('onclick', 'checkAnswer(' + questions[id].rightAnswer + ',' + key + ',' + id + ')');
        answerButton.appendTo(answerButtonDiv);

    });

    	{
		question: "What's in a Vodka Martini?",
		answer: "cold vodka, dry vermouth"
	},
	
	{
		question: "What's in a Manhattan?",
		answer: "whiskey, sweet vermouth"
	},

	{
		question: "What's in a Rusty Nail?",
		answer: "scotch, drambuie"
	},

	{
		question: "What's in a Long Island Iced Tea?",
		answer: "rum, gin, vodka, tequila, triple sec, sour mix, cola"
	},

	{
		question: "What's in a Tom Collins?",
		answer: "lemon, syrup, club soda"
	},

	{
		question: "What's in a Old Fashioned?",
		answer: "whiskey, sugar, bitters, orange"
	},

	{
		question: "What's in a Bellini?",
		answer: "prosecco/champagne, peach juice"
		
	},

	{
		question: "What's in a Sex on the Beach?",
		answer: "vodka, peach schnapps, creme de cassis, orange and cranberry juices"
	},

	{
		question: "What's in a Margarita?",
		answer: "tequila, triple sec, lime juice"
	},

	{
		question: "What's in a Cosmopolitan?",
		answer: "vodka, cranberry juice, cointreu, lime juice"
	},
] ; */